<wgp sitename="WoW Guru" url="http://wowguru.com/ui/">
	<file name="Ultimate UI" author="nathanmx" email="" url="http://wowguru.com/ui/ultimate-ui-id4" currentversion="9.8.2 default">
		<description>[b]Latest News about UUI can always be found at:[/b]
[url=http://www.wowbattle.net/portal.php]WoWBattle.net[/url] - News and information site for Ultimate UI

[url=http://www.wowbattle.net/index.php]forums[/url] | [url=http://www.wowbattle.net/portal.php]uui information site[/url]

[b]What is Ultimate UI?[/b]
Ultimate UI, often abbreviated as &quot;UUI&quot;, is an addon package for World of Warcraft that extends the functionality of the game, making it easier and more efficient to perform a wide range of tasks.

Let's get real with one thing here: all these UI packages can be pretty darn complicated. I'm not going to say UUI is the best, I'm not going to say UUI is always super easy to setup, but I am going to say this: Ultimate UI has as many if not more features than most other UI's, and if you play your cards right and have the patience to set it up, it can be far more powerful than any other UI on the market. It's really that simple.
As of the next version, there will be three different versions of UUI.

1. Simpleton (Beginner)
This style is exactly that - simple and sweet. Most of the default UI graphics remain unaltered, though you still get the power and many of the features that UUI can provide. Requires minimal setup.

2. Reawakening (Intermediate)
This style is essentially the same as the Simpleton UI but with one key distinction - the default actions bars are removed and replaced with Discord Action Bars (DAB). DAB is a seemingly thorough yet surprisingly simple way to set up a multitude of action bars on your screen. It can be overwhelming at first, but this soon goes away as you understand it. Furthermore, this UI features artwork called &quot;Reawakening&quot; by Raeken. The challenge of this setup is using MoveAnything to move and size the Reawakening art to fit your screen, moving the minimap and other frames to their appropriate places, and using Discord Action Bars to place buttons on top of the artwork.

3. Druidium (Advanced)
Druidium is art that goes with the entire Discord package. Included is Discord Action Bars, Discord Unit Frames, Discord Library, and Discord Art. They all operate independantly, which can be confusing at times. They are all very complex, and although setting up this UI might actually be EASIER than the begginner UI (due to being able to load custom settings), actually changing stuff should you not like the setup can prove quite time consuming. This will probably be the choice for many people, and it is quite rewarding to see the finished product. It's a work of art to behold - and when combined with the rest of Ultimate UI, it's simply... a masterpiece.
</description>
		<addons>
			<addon>MetaMapFWM</addon>
			<addon>CT_RABossMods</addon>
			<addon>SuperInspect</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_CraftUI</addon>
			<addon>DynamicDataItem</addon>
			<addon>TitanPerformance</addon>
			<addon>TitanXP</addon>
			<addon>UUIVersion</addon>
			<addon>GoodInspect</addon>
			<addon>DefendYourself</addon>
			<addon>Slash_GM</addon>
			<addon>SimpleMail</addon>
			<addon>FlightTime</addon>
			<addon>TrinketMenu</addon>
			<addon>EnchanterAdShrinker</addon>
			<addon>Wardrobe</addon>
			<addon>CCWatch</addon>
			<addon>CleanMinimap</addon>
			<addon>TitanLootType</addon>
			<addon>Sea</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_RaidUI</addon>
			<addon>Carnival_EnemyCastBar</addon>
			<addon>TitanRider</addon>
			<addon>TitanItemBonuses</addon>
			<addon>CT_RaidAssist</addon>
			<addon>Backdrop</addon>
			<addon>NotesUNeed</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_AuctionUI</addon>
			<addon>SuperInspect_UI</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_InspectUI</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_TrainerUI</addon>
			<addon>WatchTower</addon>
			<addon>TooltipsBase</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_MacroUI</addon>
			<addon>SimpleTip</addon>
			<addon>TrackerAssist</addon>
			<addon>SelfCast</addon>
			<addon>TitanCoords</addon>
			<addon>TitanMoney</addon>
			<addon>MegaMacro</addon>
			<addon>DynamicData</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_BattlefieldMinimap</addon>
			<addon>linkSnag</addon>
			<addon>TitanHonorPlus</addon>
			<addon>TitanBag</addon>
			<addon>TitanSpeed</addon>
			<addon>Titan</addon>
			<addon>QuickLoot</addon>
			<addon>TitanRepair</addon>
			<addon>!ImprovedErrorFrame</addon>
			<addon>TitanRegen</addon>
			<addon>sct</addon>
			<addon>QuickMountEquip</addon>
			<addon>TitanClock</addon>
			<addon>MetaMap</addon>
			<addon>TitanStanceSets</addon>
			<addon>Confab</addon>
			<addon>TitanAmmo</addon>
			<addon>MoveAnything</addon>
			<addon>UltimateUI</addon>
			<addon>CallToArms</addon>
			<addon>MozzFullWorldMap</addon>
			<addon>Gatherer</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_TalentUI</addon>
			<addon>AllInOneInventory</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_TradeSkillUI</addon>
			<addon>QuestLevels</addon>
			<addon>whopinged</addon>
			<addon>AvailableOnly</addon>
			<addon>CharactersViewer</addon>
			<addon>Blizzard_BindingUI</addon>
			<addon>QuuSpellAlert</addon>
			<addon>DamageMeters</addon>
			<addon>LS_Chat</addon>
		</addons>
			<category id=""></category>		<version number="9.8.2 default" date="0">
			<file url="http://wowguru.com/ui/archives/ultimate-ui-4-982-default.zip" checksum="" />
		</version>
	</file>
</wgp>
