<wgp sitename="WoW Guru" url="http://wowguru.com/ui/">
	<file name="MozzFullWorldMap (Fan's Update)" author="Telic" email="" url="http://wowguru.com/ui/mozzfullworldmap-fans-update-id239" currentversion="v2.05.11200">
		<description>MozzFullWorldMap v2.00.11200

Now compatible with AlphaMap

MozzFullWorldMap is simple: it adds a new checkbox in the upper left of the world map named 'Show Unexplored Areas'. Checking it will do just that.

The default settings mean that unexplored areas appear with a blue/green tinge. I believe this setting is the most useful as it means that you can see all the details of the map, while still being able to identify which areas you have not yet explored.
You can change the behaviour of the AddOn via the Slash commands detailed below, and remove the blue tinge completely, leaving you with a standard view of each map as though you had already explored every area :)

This AddOn is compatible with :
WorldMapFrame,
AlphaMap,
MetaMap (you should disable MetaMapFWM if using this AddOn)


 //// DISCLAIMER / APOLOGY / CREDIT ////

Original AddOn by Mozz

Resurrected by Shub as MozzFullWorldMap 1.10 + configurable

As Shub is no longer maintaining his version he has given me permission to release this version based on his work.

I am releasing this version simply to make its functionality accessible from the 'AlphaMap (Fan's Update)' AddOn - so when you have both this AddOn, and AlphaMap installed - unexplored areas can be displayed in AlphaMap :)

/////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////////


Slash Commands
--------------

/mozzfullworldmap blue: unexplored areas in a pretty blue color
/mozzfullworldmap normal: unexplored areas in normal worldmap color
/mozzfullworldmap trans [0.0-1.0]: sets transparency, 0.0 is completely clear up to 1.0 which is completely opaque.

/mfwm can also be used to access these commands.

Note for mod developers: MozzFullWorldMap short-circuits the overlay code in WorldMapFrame_Update() for performance. Because of this, GetNumMapOverlays() will always return 0. Use Mozz_GetNumMapOverlays() instead, or contact me if this isn't possible.

To install, unzip into the WoW game directory. Make sure you have 'extract with pathnames' or the equivalent selected in your unzip program.


This version has been released to allow unexplored areas to be displayed in the 'AlphaMap (Fan's Update)' AddOn, when both are installed alongside each other.


This version is called MozzFullWorldMap (Fan's Update), but it will install to the original MozzFullWorldMap directory and overwrite previous versions of the original, or Shub's version. It is displayed in the AddOns list simply as MozzFullWorldMap. I have released this version starting at v2.00 to break away from previous version numbering.</description>
		<addons>
			<addon>MozzFullWorldMap</addon>
		</addons>
			<category id=""></category>		<version number="v2.05.11200" date="1148672513">
			<file url="http://wowguru.com/ui/archives/mozzfullworldmap-fans-update-239-v20511200.zip" checksum="" />
		</version>
	</file>
</wgp>
