<Addon name="Opium" author="Oystein" email="" url="http://www.wowguru.com/ui/opium">
	<Description>Opium is a tool for managing KoS lists, keeping track of PvP (and duel) stats and generally storing player info.

Some of its features, in brief:
* Player and Guild KoS (Kill on Sight) lists. Several ways of adding to these lists.
* KoS lists can be sent to other players, if both of you have Sky (and Opium) installed .
* If you encounter a player you've designated as KoS, there are several ways Opium can let you know. Sound alerts, text alerts, and tooltip/targetframe text.
* Opium can keep track of who have killed you and who you have killed, and generate statistics for this.
* A list of players you've seen and their info (race, class, guild, guild rank, etc) can be stored. It's completely up to you who is stored, and there are functions to selectively search, sort and purge this list.


It's designed to be as flexible and as configurable as possible (always several ways of doing things, and everything is optional). It's a completely stand-alone AddOn, with myAddOns support, and should
work with any UI compilation (Cosmos, CTMod, Nurfed, Gypsy, etc).

Please read the readme.txt file included in the archive for more detailed documentation.


-------------------------------------------


Contact:
Please send any comments/suggestions/bug reports to opium AT geheb DOT com, or post them here. Or look me up on Bleeding Hollow/Horde, name Oystein.

Credit:
Thanks to Telo for LootLink, which I've a lot of UI code from.
Thanks to Radon for the German localization, and Greg for the French localization. And thanks to Sykotic for the button graphics!

Note:
I've designed the data structures to use minimal memory. Even if you
set up Opium to store the info of every player you come across, the the memory usage is quite minimal. 3000 recorded players will take up somewhat in excess of 300 KBs on disk.</Description>
	<UpdateFile listed="true" url="http://www.wowguru.com/ui/opium/xml/" />
	<CurrentVersion ver="2.6" />
</Addon>